[
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "Load Testing",
    "option 4": "Unit Testing",
    "question": "Which is not part of system testing?",
    "option 1": "Regression Testing",
    "option 2": "Sanity Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "Integration Testing",
    "option 4": "Acceptance Testing",
    "question": "Which testing ensures that changes do not affect existing functionality?",
    "option 1": "Unit Testing",
    "option 2": "Regression Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 1,
    "option 3": "Smoke Testing",
    "option 4": "Acceptance Testing",
    "question": "What type of testing is performed without documentation?",
    "option 1": "Ad-hoc Testing",
    "option 2": "System Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "Unit Testing",
    "option 4": "System Testing",
    "question": "Which testing is done by end-users or customers?",
    "option 1": "Integration Testing",
    "option 2": "Acceptance Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "Unit Testing",
    "option 4": "Sanity Testing",
    "question": "Which type of testing focuses on performance under load?",
    "option 1": "Smoke Testing",
    "option 2": "Stress Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Test Plan",
    "option 4": "Requirement Specification",
    "question": "What document describes the test objectives, scope, strategy, and resources required for testing?",
    "option 1": "Test Case",
    "option 2": "Bug Report"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Unit Testing",
    "option 4": "User Acceptance Testing (UAT)",
    "question": "The phase where individual software components are tested is called:",
    "option 1": "System Testing",
    "option 2": "Integration Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 2,
    "option 3": "To measure code coverage",
    "option 4": "To test the performance under load",
    "question": "What is the primary goal of Black Box Testing?",
    "option 1": "To examine the internal structure and code",
    "option 2": "To verify system functionality against requirements"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 4,
    "option 3": "Security Testing",
    "option 4": "User Acceptance Testing (UAT)",
    "question": "Which type of testing verifies that the software meets the needs of the end-user",
    "option 1": "Stress Testing",
    "option 2": "Performance Testing"
  },
  {
    "answerkey": 3,
    "option 3": "Test Execution Log",
    "option 4": "3",
    "question": "Requirement Traceability Matrix",
    "option 1": "Test Summary Report",
    "option 2": "Bug Report (or Defect Report)"
  }
]